<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheatsheets on </title>
    <link>https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cheatsheets on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory (AD) Attacks</title>
      <link>https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/adattacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/adattacks/</guid>
      <description>AD Attack Cheatsheet Description: This is going to be a compilation of my notes on various Active Directory (AD) attacks. I may dive deeper into some attacks and go over creating a homelab vulnerable to these attacks and dive into tools to execute these attacks as well
 ASREPRoastable Accounts - Active Directory user accounts that have the DO NOT REQUIRE KERBEROS PREAUTHENTICATION property enabled. This allows an attacker to request a Kerberos ticket without having to provide a password for preauthentication, just the username and the domain which can be easily found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Active Directory (AD) Basics</title>
      <link>https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/adbasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1d8.github.io/cheatsheets/adbasics/</guid>
      <description>Description: Notes taken from the TryHackMe room AD Basics. Will likely add to this as I progress in my AD adventure
Overview  What AD is? What an AD domain is? What components go into an AD domain Forests &amp;amp; Domain trusts etc  Windows Domains Windows Domains is a group of users &amp;amp; computers under the administration of a given business
 The main idea/goal is centralizing the administration of those components of a Windows network into a single repository called Active Directory (AD)  The server running the AD services is called the Domain Controller (DC)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
